(Previously)
If you don't want to borrow my money,
how about you let me invest in your company?
No one has ever believed in me
this much in my entire life.
I don't even know what I'll be like
when I get out of the military.
When my friend moves to Dubai,
I'll definitely miss him.
Next time, please tell me things right away.
Don't let me find out from someone else.
But I'm so happy for you.
You made your dream come true.
The foundation just called.
A plane crashed.
Hey!
Please check on Kanit.
- His leg is badly hurt.
- Are you okay?
Just the thought of losing you
is more than I can bear.
Ouch!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Why didn't you tell me what you wanted?
Come here.
Be gentle.
What do you want?
My phone.
Here.
The rice porridge is ready.
I made you an omelet too.
It looks so good.
Come on.
Food is served. Enjoy.
What did the doctor say yesterday?
When can you get your cast off?
In about two weeks.
Is it itchy?
A little.
I'll scratch it for you.
Hey.
Go deeper.
A little deeper.
Yes, right there.
Ah, so good.
Right there.
Ah.
A little harder.
If you're itchy somewhere else,
I can help with that too.
For free.
You pervert.
My leg hurts. Who would be in the mood?
Well…
Just in case you are.
Are you really not in the mood?
No.
Is it still itchy?
Not anymore.
Hey, while your leg is like this,
you need to keep it elevated
so it doesn't swell.
Ouch!
It feels tight.
Just sit like this.
Once you're done eating, take your medicine.
This one's for after your meal.
This helps with the pain.
This reduces swelling.
You remember everything so well,
even though you're not the one taking them.
That's because I pay attention.
Ow! That hurts!
I'm taking you
to get your dressing changed this afternoon.
Does it smell yet?
Gross.
You're a flight attendant with a broken wing.
I have to take good care of you.
Come on.
Eat it while it's still hot.
This smells so good. Come on.
It's skinless chicken.
Blow on it for me.
I'm just testing it for you.
Ugh, gross.
Come on.
What are you looking at?
What?
In two days?
Mm.
But look at me.
I don't think I can make it.
Why don't you call them?
Just tell them you have an emergency.
Ask if you can postpone it.
You can join the next round.
I can't do that.
No one does that.
The next round probably won't be
until next year.
Then I'm taking you.
To where?
To talk to the airline.
Come on.
Let's go now.
Hey.
Slowly.
Hold on.
Are you sure you're okay?
Don't push yourself. You'll hurt your back.
It's your dream.
If I can't be a flight attendant,
there are other things I can do.
I'm so lucky to have even survived
that accident.
I have no dreams left
other than spending time with you.
"A Dog and A Plane"
(Episode 10)
Here.
Damn, I feel so bad for you.
You only just started teaching here.
Yeah.
I was having fun.
I thought I could make it long-term.
Seriously, man.
Things were just starting
to get back on track for you.
But you should be fine.
It's only two years.
You can come back and apply again.
Two whole years.
Who knows what opportunities I'll miss,
instead of getting to do what I love?
It's okay.
You can always come back.
Yeah.
Bye.
Get home safe.
VEHA
Bye.
WHY WON'T YOU PICK UP THE PHONE?
I'M TEACHING.
STANDING AT THE GATE DOESN'T
REALLY COUNT AS TEACHING.
- Bye.
Come on!
Focus!
Move over!
Faster!
Come on!
You won't pick up the phone
or reply to my texts.
Why are you avoiding me?
I've been busy.
Handling my resignation,
handing over my classes.
Not to mention,
preparing my paperwork for the military.
Stop with your excuses.
It's just picking up the phone.
Is it that hard?
You're not even looking at me
when I'm talking to you right now.
Look at me.
Say what's on your mind.
I'll be away for two years.
I don't want you to wait for me.
Why did you say that?
We've talked about this.
You'll hang in there, and I'll wait.
I don't want a promise to tie us down.
It's a whole two years.
If you find someone better than me,
you deserve it.
You deserve to find someone
with a better future.
Why are you assuming things on your own?
These are my feelings. I'll deal with them.
These are my feelings too.
I don't want you to worry.
I don't know what's going to happen to me.
What's going to happen to you?
You'll be fine.
I'll visit you.
And then you'll get out of there.
Telling me to find someone else
is so insulting.
Do you know how many years I waited
for you before we got together?
What makes you think
I can't wait another two damn years?
What's wrong with you?
Hello.
(Hello. I'm calling from Magic Sky Airway.)
Oh, hello.
(We'd like you to come in
for reporting and training.)
(The management was impressed)
(by how you helped the passengers
during the accident the other day.)
Really?
Thank you.
(You're welcome.
We'll send you the details by email.)
Sure. Thank you so much.
To!
Hey! What's wrong?
Hey.
Magic Sky Airway called me in to start.
Oh!
I'm happy for you!
Hey.
Are you really happy?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm happy for you.
But I'm worried about you.
You just got into an accident.
I don't want you to go through
anything like that again.
You know that accidents can't be predicted.
You should know that better than anyone.
I understand.
It's your dream.
I'm willing to support you.
But I'm going to be based overseas.
What about our business?
Don't worry about that.
I'll take care of it.
That's my dream too.
Let's each chase our own dreams,
then meet back in the middle for ours.
Is that okay?
I'm so lucky to have a boyfriend
who understands me.
I'm so damn proud of you.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I guess we have to shower together now.
What are you working on?
A will leaving all your assets to me?
Whoa.
Wishing me dead already?
Come on.
Breaking down all this money?
What else could it be?
Saving up money to get married?
Look.
How could I marry anyone
with just this much money?
Oh, bro.
Why is love so expensive?
Can't you just show your sincerity
and make a promise?
Being romantic doesn't pay the bills.
You need money in your bank account
to prove it.
Love has no place for poor people, huh?
I'll work hard when I grow up.
- Je, hi.
- Oh.
It's the wrong time to be craving
minced meat salad.
I'm here to talk business.
Scammer!
- Serving politicians!
- No!
If it's shady, I'm out.
Don't even ask me.
It's nothing like that.
You're already rich. I don't even need to ask.
I want to rent the second floor for my office.
No way.
What?
Isn't that too fast?
No way.
Je!
We can discuss the rent.
No way!
Je!
I'm giving it to you for free.
I don't want to run a minced meat salad business.
Oh, I'm definitely not
letting you take over my business.
If I gave you my recipe,
you'd only ruin it.
Now that I think about it,
what happened that day
made me realize
life is so short.
You never know if you'll die tomorrow.
Who am I talking to?
- I'm here.
- Yeah.
I've saved money my whole life.
Who knows if I'll ever get to spend it?
So I've decided.
I'm going to travel.
I'm going to spend all my money
traveling the world.
See the wonders of the Ancient World,
the Middle Ages, and the New World.
I'll see it all.
I'm sure there must be another Stonehenge
and another pyramid somewhere else.
Must be nice to be rich.
You get to do everything you want.
Don't be jealous of me.
This building is yours.
But…
give me my shares.
Who knows?
If your business hits it big
and becomes a unicorn like Komsan Lee's,
I'm going to sell my shares
and use the money to explore
the wonders outside the world.
So let me learn an alien language now.
Je! Be serious!
Do you see the potential
or just sympathize with me?
I sympathize with you.
Seriously?
Look, To.
I see your effort.
If I don't see the value
and help someone who's trying,
who the hell do you expect me to help?
So I'll be able to save up faster
for my marriage.
When you're a CEO,
everyone wants you to be their son-in-law.
Thank you, Je.
Can I get a hug?
What?
No!
You're so kind!
It kinda feels like I'm your dad and mom.
You're both.
Je!
Hey, Ki.
Aren't you taking shifts
at the foundation anymore?
Are you busy?
I just don't want him to find me there.
Who?
Veha?
I'm going into the army in just a few days.
I don't want to see him.
I'm scared I'll cave
and try to make up with him.
Please. You're scared of caving?
What you're doing to him
is so mean, you know?
You don't need to rub it in.
Did you eat all my gummies?
Yeah.
It's good.
I'll grab more.
Wow, you're complaining?
Alright.
I won't rub salt in the wound.
But I'm going to say something,
and it's not that I'm trying to lecture you.
Soon, you won't get to see him anymore.
So I think you should
use the time you have left
to see him.
Stop with your romantic act.
That's so outdated.
Love is a sacrifice?
That's ancient, Ki.
If you really love him, you have to be selfish.
You shouldn't let him find someone better,
because you're the best.
You think I should see him?
At least, if he comes to see you,
just don't run away.
Mm.
Okay.
Mm. Good.
There he is.
How did you get here?
I saw Beer when I went to the foundation.
He told me to come find you here.
Why did you cut your hair like that?
Why are you doing this?
I want to show you that I'm sincere.
I even prepared a military application.
So neither of us has to wait for each other.
I'm going in with you.
Are you crazy?
You can't leave your good life for me.
My good life
means having you in it.
I won't give up.
I won't let you leave me.
I waited for so long before we got together.
Nothing can stop us now.
Except you,
who's scared of god knows what.
I never want to leave you, Veha.
I just want you to find someone better.
There's no one better.
My heart is with you.
What can I do to make you believe me?
Squat jump 100 times?
Hey!
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for underestimating your heart.
Don't ever say you'll leave me again.
This haircut looks hot on you.
Pretty sexy. I like it.
Sexy? It's so dorky.
But if it could make you believe
that I'll wait for you, I'm okay with it.
Okay.
I believe you now.
Please fasten your seatbelts.
Sir,
please adjust your seat
to the upright position.
Thank you.
What?
What's going on?
May I help you with anything?
Oh.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to make your dream come true.
Hey.
You're making a scene.
Aren't you disturbing the other passengers?
I already told everyone.
They're willing to be my witness.
Right?
Yes.
Alright.
What did you prepare to surprise me?
No surprise.
I'm just a handsome, rugged guy
who loves you as much as the sky.
Ready to get down on one knee
and tell my boyfriend.
I'm ready to take care of him
for the rest of his life.
I've barked at the plane for too long.
Today, they let this dog on the plane.
Will you take this dog flying with you?
Well, if this dog is going to be this romantic,
I'll take him around the world.
No.
Do it again. Say it properly.
You're not a dog anymore.
We're equal now.
Neither is on the ground or in the sky.
Get up.
Then I'll keep it simple, Sek Loso style.
Nit, I love you so f*cking much.
Will you marry me?
Of course, it's a yes.
I freaking will.
Kiss!
That's enough. Thank you.
That's enough.
♪ Fly with me, free my heart ♪
♪ Don't be shy, just open your heart ♪
♪ Wanna come aboard, give it a try ♪
♪ Love is gonna take off now ♪
♪ Our love is gonna take off now ♪
You should go.
So I can go in there.
You walk in first.
I'll see you off until the last second.
How can I not be sad when you say that?
Who knows
when we'll see each other again?
Or when we'll hug
or kiss again.
Hey.
A soldier can come out
and visit their partner.
Aren't you going to visit me?
I don't know
what I'm going to face in the military.
You'll face nothing.
When you get out,
you'll look even more handsome.
But if you find—
I won't.
I'll wait for you.
I'll wait to kiss you again.
Okay.
I believe you now.
If a soldier hits on me,
I'll tell him my boyfriend is waiting.
Every time I do push-ups,
I'll think of your face.
Every time I practice my aim,
you'll be my goal.
Are you going to shoot me?
Mm.
Shoot you with a kiss.
Go now,
so I can go inside.
If you don't go, I will.
I'll be waiting.
Smile for me.
I'll remember your face when I miss you.
I'm off.
Oh, shit!
Dad!
Hi, Dad.
Whose dad?
Who's your dad?
Dad.
Why won't you give him a proper welcome?
I don't want to welcome a liar.
Can you at least welcome the guy
who saved your life?
Why are you here?
I have a project to pitch.
What project?
I've come to ask for Kanit's hand in marriage.
You've got some nerve.
What makes you think you're good enough
to come into my home and ask for my son?
Dad, um…
Don't speak.
I'm asking him.
He has to answer.
All my answers are right here.
Beer.
SAVINGS ACCOUNT
Currently,
this is how much I've saved in my account.
EVERYTHING TOTO
ALL-IN-ONE EMERGENCY ASSISTANCE
And this is the 20-year strategic plan
for Kanit and me.
We're investing in a company called.
Everything Toto.
Dad, Mom, you're probably wondering
what this company is all about.
Allow me to explain.
This company provides all kinds of services.
From emergency assistance,
car washes, auto repairs,
tree trimming, to pet care
and delivery services.
We solve whatever problems
people are facing.
Our 5-year plan is to expand our team.
Our 10-year plan
is to open new branches.
And our 20-year plan
is to give Kanit a stable life
and make him the richest man
in the lower south,
right around the Andaman Basin.
All-in-one. Done by Everything Toto.
Wow!
That's really amazing.
That's the end of my proposal presentation.
I like it.
I approve.
But I still don't like it.
Why not, Dad?
He just said he can take care of me.
The important thing I want to hear about
isn't money.
What I want to know is
why it has to be my son Kanit.
Because …
it's my heart's command.
Come on, Toto!
This is not the time to quote P'Sek.
Give a serious answer.
I am being serious.
My feelings are following
my heart's command.
I've liked Kanit since the day I got out of
the car and called him Boiling Tofu.
Who else could keep up with
my sharp tongue like he does?
And look at him.
His face. His skin.
He checks every single box for me.
How can anyone say
that's not my heart's command?
Hey.
Answer me, not your friend.
Sorry, Dad.
But it's true.
Ever since I met Kanit,
I started taking vitamins.
Are you kidding?
Are you serious right now?
Of course, I'm serious.
Ever since I met Kanit,
I started taking vitamins
because I want to take good care
of my health
so I can keep taking care of him
for a long time.
He takes care of me so well.
I'm never letting him go.
I already love it.
What should we do, hon?
Well, I love it.
I'm sold.
I'm buying your sincerity.
You've made me see
that my son has a place in your future.
You're for real. You pass.
You have my permission
to be my future son-in-law
from this moment on.
You did it.
But don't you ever break my son's heart,
or you'll take a bullet.
Don't worry, Dad.
With me, he'll never shed a tear.
Hooo...
Ho-ho-ho-ho…
Hiew!
Ho…
He-o-he-o-he-o-he-o…
Hiew!
Hooo...
Ho-ho-ho-ho…
Hiew!
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Can I pass through?
Hold on.
Before you pass,
you have to give us the Southern password.
Oh, there's something Kanit always says.
“Motherf*cker.”
“F*cking hell.”
“D*ckhead.”
This is an auspicious occasion.
It's not those words.
Oh, no?
No.
But Kanit always says those things.
Oh, I know what it is.
“I'm not someone who talks nonsense.
I always speak the truth. I don't lie.
“I'm devoted to one love. If you don't believe me,
go see a tiger riding a monkey.
“If it's not true,
go see a monkey riding a tiger!”
There it is.
Pass on through.
Thank you.
Pailin.
Please go easy on me.
Mr. Toto.
You want to marry a flight attendant.
I want to know if you even know
how to make an in-flight announcement.
That's not beyond me.
Yeah!
Let's hear it.
This is the final call
for Everything Toto Airlines.
Flight TT 216,
now boarding for Kanit's heart.
All passengers,
please proceed to Toto's heart.
How did I do?
Did I pass?
You passed!
You're cleared for takeoff.
Thank you.
This way.
Hello, Dad and Mom.
Hello.
Are you ready to accept a rescue worker
as your son-in-law?
Ready, hon?
I've been ready for a long time.
My son-in-law is so handsome.
Amazing.
WEDDING CEREMONY
KANIT & PANUPONG 12 DECEMBER 2026
Do you like the dress I bought you?
Is it to your liking?
It's pretty, Mom.
I'm so glad to be here today.
To see your brother happy.
Just this chance from him
takes a huge weight of guilt off my chest,
even though he doesn't let me
be a part of his life.
He might change his mind one day.
Come on. Let's take some photos together.
Okay.
Let's see.
One. Two. Three.
Cheers!
Hey.
Honestly,
I can't believe
rescue workers like us
get to hang out with people in this league.
Yeah.
You know what?
I might go for a walk around the airport.
Maybe I'll run into a handsome captain
or flight attendant.
Oh, Pailin.
Do you have any handsome guys
to introduce me to?
I know a few.
See?
- Here we go.
- But a captain?
If I find one, I'm keeping him for myself.
Queen move.
As she should.
There goes my chance of getting my wings.
This girl stole it.
But before we get to your happy ending,
we should keep our fingers crossed
for Ki and Veha.
Yeah.
I don't know.
When it comes to this, I shouldn't be
the only one talking about it, right?
He needs to say it, too.
It's not like I don't want to,
but he hasn't asked yet.
I have to wait for him to finish
his military service first.
- Got it.
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers?
Let's drink to drown our worries!
Yeah!
Woo!
Bottoms up.
Seriously?
If I asked,
would you say yes?
Hey.
Ki!
I thought you weren't coming.
It's my dear brother's wedding.
How could I miss it?
Sit down, bro.
You should've told us you were coming.
Come on.
Besides,
I missed my boyfriend so bad.
Oh!
Stop it.
If you missed me,
why didn't you call me more often?
Yeah.
My training has been super intense.
They took my phone.
I've tried my best.
Please don't be mad at me.
Please don't sulk.
We don't get to see each other often.
I won't sulk.
I'd rather spend our time loving each other
and making everyone here jealous.
Sure.
- He was looking this way.
- I'm so jealous.
Por, I want that!
Wait until you're a big girl.
Stop it.
I know I'm only 156 cm tall.
Enough.
Let's make them even more jealous.
Bro!
You guys are stealing the spotlight
from the hosts!
Our wedding can't be any less grand
than To's.
I wouldn't let anyone outdo me.
Oh!
I can't wait to see it.
Hello. One. Two. Three.
And now,
I'd like to invite Village Head Kwaed
to come up
and offer a blessing to the newlyweds.
Thank you.
The groom and I
have known each other for a long time.
His name is… Kanit.
We're neighbors.
I've seen him since he was a kid.
And today, he's finally settling down
and starting his own family.
Being life partners is a journey.
Hold hands tightly
through thick and thin.
I wish for you to be life partners
who are best friends—
knowing each other's hearts,
and understanding each other forever.
Thank you.
You know the village head?
I've never met him before.
Thank you so much, sir,
for honoring us
by wishing the newlyweds well.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Next,
I'd like to invite the newlyweds
to say a few words to our guests.
To!
(Shut up!)
Alright.
Thank you to all our honored guests
for coming to our wedding.
I don't have much to say,
except that from now on,
no matter what comes our way,
I promise we'll face
and get through it all together.
Come on. Say something.
I don't like public speaking.
Just say anything.
Woo!
Alright.
I…
I'm not good with words.
But I actually have something to say
to everyone.
I think
the electricity bill has been
so expensive lately.
And you guys are using a lot of power.
Look.
You turned on so many lights.
It's so bright out here.
But there's this one light
that shines the brightest in my heart.
This one.
Hell no, I'm not letting you get married!
Definitely not!
That's right!
What's going on?
Is he your ex?
No.
- I don't even know who he is.
- Oh?
Once you get married,
you're just gonna end up divorced anyway!
Love isn't real!
Love makes you blind!
Yeah!
That you can't see the truth!
He's quoting Toon Bodyslam.
What's going on?
Weddings are nonsense!
How is he that drunk?
Hey!
He's having a seizure!
Why are these people lying on the ground?
What's going on?
How are they?
Could it be the bootleg liquor?
Bootleg liquor?
He's drooling.
- What should we do?
- I'm going to check on them.
I'll help.
To.
Tong, Beer, Ki, check on them.
Give them first aid.
Okay.
Sure.
Let's go.
Ja-O, radio for backup at the scene immediately.
And get a sample of that liquor.
Okay.
He's already drooling.
Hey.
Can I get a cloth to rest his head on?
- Sure.
- Bring it now.
Everyone, please stay back.
Give us some space.
Let us clear the area.
Please don't crowd around.
Look!
Excuse me.
Here you go.
I appreciate your help, Ki.
You came straight from the military
and didn't even get a chance to rest.
Damn.
It's okay.
I could really use some excitement
in my life right now.
Thanks a lot for coming all the way
to my wedding.
Congratulations.
But honestly, your wedding
isn't as important
as seeing my boyfriend.
Yeah, I know.
I'm heading out now.
I've been deprived for too long.
Time to get some action.
You're so annoying.
Hurry up and get going.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
It was supposed to be an auspicious day,
but we had to deal with all that.
I'm a rescue worker.
That's a 24/7 job.
See?
Being with me takes toughness.
You risk both body and heart.
Yeah, I know.
If I weren't willing to take that risk,
I wouldn't have married you.
Well, the wedding turned into
a complete disaster.
That was such a life-and-death moment.
You and I will never live in peace.
There'll always be chaos
to keep us entertained.
Let's keep loving, bickering,
and fighting like this forever.
Can we just love each other?
No more fighting. It's exhausting.
How about fighting in bed instead?
Your mind is always in the gutter.
Say something romantic for once.
I don't know how to be romantic.
I only know how to be blunt.
Alright, just be blunt then.
As long as I get to marry you,
it doesn't matter
if I have enough to get by or not.
It doesn't matter if I'm dirt poor.
I can sleep anywhere,
as long as I get to sleep
next to you.
Oh.
You're copying P'Sek again.
Come on. He's my idol
when it comes to romance.
Will you accept my love,
Mr. Boiling Tofu?
Of course, I will.
Mr. Black-Smoke Barking Dog.
♪ With you and me together ♪
♪ Every day, just like this ♪
♪ Through both the good and stormy weather ♪
♪ Love needs no reason for this ♪
♪ It can't be wrong ♪
♪ To not care what people say ♪
♪ When it comes to me and you ♪
♪ We are the reason that stays ♪
Let's take this inside.
Dear passenger.
Welcome to tonight's flight.
Please check your seat.
Exits are located at the front
and back of the cabin.
In case of emergency, please remain calm
and follow the cabin crew's instructions.
It's my first time flying first class.
I don't understand anything.
In that case,
please start by
unbuttoning your shirt.
What's next?
Now, what would you like?
Coffee?
Or tea?
Or me?
What should I get?
I can't hold it anymore.
Can we start now?
Sir, please.
No sexual harassment of the cabin crew.
I'm not your passenger.
I'm your husband.
Stop staring.
We're about to bang.